Selva S

Digital Marketing Executive

CONTACT

Phone +91 7812062930

Email infoselva66@gmail.com

Location Tenkasi, Tamil Nadu

LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/selva-s-

64556b218/

Instagram www.instagram.com/am_the_sel

va?

igsh=MWdqdm9tZGlhYXNqdg==

X SKILLS

Digital Marketing Skills

Keyword optimization | Google Analytics | Search Engine Optimization (SEO) | Google Ads | Social Media Optimization (SMO)

Other Skills

Microsoft Office | Tally ERP | Excell - Vlook Up , Pivot Table etc

SOFTWARE

Google Analytics | Google Search Console | Semrush | Ubersuggest | Meta Business Suite | Google Keyword Planner

🖳 LANGUAGES

Tamil | English

OBJECTIVE

I am a Digital Marketing Professional with a Diploma in Digital Marketing. I Have Experience in Creating and Executing Digital Marketing Campaigns, Managing Social media accounts, Conducting Market Research and analyzing data to optimize marketing strategies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Digital Marketing Intern

rn Mar 2023 - May 2023

E - Search Advisors, Chennai

- I finished My internship at E-search Advisors.
- As an Intern, I worked on SEO on-page and off-page to their websites, creating landing pages as well.
- I Ran Google Ads and paid ads using Meta Business Suite.
- I've worked on Social Media pages to generate organic traffic to social media accounts.

Process Associate

Aug 2023 - Feb 2024

Cognet Hr Solutions, Chennai

- Understanding the client requirements and configuring the software to address these requirements. - Collect daily, Weekly, Bi-weekly, Monthly.
- Semi-Monthly timesheets. Prepare employee by the end of each month using payroll software.
- Enter new employee's data (e.g. bank accounts and tax identification numbers) into internal databases. Hands-on experience with HRIS and accounting software.
- Prepare and execute pay orders through an electronic system or distribute paychecks. Process taxes and payment of employee benefits.
- Keep track of hours rates, wages, compensation benefit rates, new hire information, etc.
- Finally with client confirmation we will process the payroll.

EDUCATION

Higher Secondary Exam (TN HSC):Jun 2017 - Apr 2018 Computer Commerce Mark: 753

Deepa Matriculation Higher Secondary School

Bachelor of Commerce (ComputerJul 2018 - Aug 2021

Application): B.Com(CA) 77%

Srinivasan College of Arts and Science

👼 CERTIFICATIONS

Diploma In Office and Accounting Feb 2022 - Aug 2022 Software

Diploma in Digital Marketing Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

即 DECLARATION

I Here by declare that all the above information is true to the best of my Knowledge.

